{
  "id": "css-basics",
  "title": "Basic CSS quiz",
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionID": 1,
      "question": "The acronym CSS means?",
      "options": [
        "Creative Style Sheets",
        "Cascading Style Sheets",
        "Computer Style Sheets",
        "Colorful Style Sheets"
      ],
      "answer": "Cascading Style Sheets"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 2,
      "question": "CSS style that is used to style a specific HTML element using style attribute",
      "options": ["Inline CSS", "External CSS", "Internal CSS", "No CSS"],
      "answer": "Inline CSS"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 3,
      "question": "What is the selector that selects everything in the document?",
      "options": [
        "Class Selector",
        "ID Selector",
        "HTML Selector",
        "Universal Selector"
      ],
      "answer": "Universal Selector"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 4,
      "question": "The CSS unit relative to the root elementâ€™s font size",
      "options": ["rem", "em", "px", "vh"],
      "answer": "rem"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 5,
      "question": "CSS style that is used to style a specific HTML page using <style> tag",
      "options": ["Inline CSS", "External CSS", "Internal CSS", "No CSS"],
      "answer": "Internal CSS"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 6,
      "question": "This selects elements with a specific class attribute",
      "options": [
        "Class Selector",
        "ID Selector",
        "HTML Selector",
        "Universal Selector"
      ],
      "answer": "Class Selector"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 7,
      "question": "CSS style that is used to style an entire website with the use of a .css file",
      "options": ["Inline CSS", "External CSS", "Internal CSS", "No CSS"],
      "answer": "External CSS"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 8,
      "question": "This is an absolute unit used sparingly for fixed elements",
      "options": ["px", "em", "%", "rem"],
      "answer": "px"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following statements is an advantage of using CSS?",
      "options": [
        "Easier to maintain",
        "Cross-browser issues",
        "Confusion due to many CSS levels",
        "No need for HTML"
      ],
      "answer": "Easier to maintain"
    },
    {
      "questionID": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following statements is not an advantage of using CSS?",
      "options": [
        "Website speed",
        "Consistent in design",
        "Time-saving",
        "Cross-browser issues"
      ],
      "answer": "Cross-browser issues"
    }
  ]
}